let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: ' Which type of JavaScript language is ___ ?',
        answer: 'B. Object-Based',
        options: [
            "A. Object-Oriented ",
            "B. Object-Based",
            "C. Assembly-language",
            "D. High-level",
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: ' Which of the following keyword to add something in the end of the array ?',
        answer: 'C. push()',
        options: [
            "A. pop()",
            "B. shift()",
            "C. push()",
            "D. slice()",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 3,
        question: ' In JavaScript the x===y statement implies that:',
        answer: 'C. Both are equal in the value and data type.',
        options: [
            "A. Both x and y are equal in value, type and reference address as well.",
            "B. Both are x and y are equal in value only.",
            "C. Both are equal in the value and data type.",
            "D. Both are not same at all.",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 4,
        question: ' Choose the correct snippet from the following to check if the variable "a" is not equal the "NULL":',
        answer: 'A. if(a!==null)',
        options: [
            "A. if(a!==null)",
            "B. if (a!)",
            "C. if(a!null)",
            "D. if(a!=null)",
        ]
    },
    
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: ' In JavaScript, what will be used for calling the function definition expression:',
        answer: 'B. Function literal',
        options: [
            "A. Function prototype)",
            "B. Function literal",
            "C. Function calling)",
            "D. Function declaration)",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: 'Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:',
        answer: 'D. immediate if',
        options: [
            "A. Alternative to if-else",
            "B. Switch statement",
            "C. If-then-else statement",
            "D. immediate if",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 7,
        question: 'In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?',
        answer: 'B. block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement',
        options: [
            "A. Conditional block",
            "B. block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
            "C. both conditional block and a single statement",
            "D. block that contains a single statement",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 8,
        question: 'When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:',
        answer: 'D. Ignores the statements',
        options: [
            "A. Shows a warning",
            "B. Prompts to complete the statement",
            "C. Throws an error",
            "D. Ignores the statements",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 9,
        question: 'The "function" and " var" are known as:',
        answer: 'C. Declaration statements',
        options: [
            "A. Keywords",
            "B. Data types",
            "C. Declaration statements",
            "D. Prototypes",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 10,
        question: ' Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?',
        answer: 'B. The local element',
        options: [
            "A. Global variable",
            "B. The local element",
            "C. The two of the above",
            "D. None of the above",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 11,
        question: 'Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?',
        answer: 'D. Function/Method',
        options: [
            "A. Preprocessor",
            "B. Triggering Event",
            "C. RMI",
            "D. Function/Method",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 12,
        question: 'Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?',
        answer: 'A. Mutable variable',
        options: [
            "A. Mutable variable",
            "B. Dynamic variable",
            "C. Volatile variable",
            "D. Immutable variable",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 13,
        question: 'In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:',
        answer: 'C. Division by zero',
        options: [
            "A. Syntax error",
            "B. Missing of semicolons",
            "C. Division by zero",
            "D. Missing of Bracket",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 14,
        question: 'Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?',
        answer: 'B. valueOf()',
        options: [
            "A. toString()",
            "B. valueOf()",
            "C. toLocaleString()",
            "D. toPrecision()",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 15,
        question: ' Which of the following one is the property of the primary expression:',
        answer: 'D. stand-alone expressions',
        options: [
            "A. Contains only keywords",
            "B. basic expressions containing all necessary functions",
            "C. contains variable references alone",
            "D. stand-alone expressions",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 16,
        question: ' Which one of the following statement is most suitable to check if the pattern matches with the sting "text".',
        answer: 'D. text==pattern',
        options: [
            "A. test(text)",
            "B. equals(pattern)",
            "C. test(pattern)",
            "D. text==pattern",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 17,
        question: ' Which one of the following is used for the calling a function or a method in the JavaScript:',
        answer: 'C. Invocation expression',
        options: [
            "A. Property Access Expression",
            "B. Functional expression",
            "C. Invocation expression",
            "D. Primary expression",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 18,
        question: 'The "new Point(3,2)", is a kind of _______ expression',
        answer: 'A. Object Creation Expression',
        options: [
            "A. Object Creation Expression",
            "B. Primary Expression",
            "C. Invocation Expression",
            "D. Constructor Calling Expression",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 19,
        question: 'Which one of the following is an ternary operator:',
        answer: 'A. ?',
        options: [
            "A. ?",
            "B. :",
            "C. +",
            "D. -",
        ]
    },

    {
        numb: 20,
        question: 'What we will get if we compare the "one" with "8" using the less than operator ("one"<8)?',
        answer: 'A. False',
        options: [
            "A. False",
            "B. True",
            "C. NaN",
            "D. Undefined",
        ]
    },

];
















